# **Zobaida Sabah**



©+9647510653641

zobaydasabah@gmail.com

庙 Iraq, Erbil, briyti

**=** 9/May/1992

Single



#### **EDUCATIONE**

2014 BA in management & economy University of Anbar, Ramadi.

2020/ Certificate in the TOEFL English language test

# **LANGUAGES**

Arabic Native

English C2

Kurdi B1

Turkish A2

#### **MOST PROUD OF**

Effective Communication

Planning

Case Management

#### **TRAININGS**

Training course in the prevention of exploitation and sexual abuse Training course in Gender Equality.



#### **SUMMARY**

Organized, detail-oriented Social Worker with more than 2 year's of experience assessing the needs of vulnerable families, supporting, and representing adults and children and developing care plans. Confident and trustworthy Administrative with a client-focused demeanor. Strong background in providing administrative and finance support in busy office environments. An expert communicator who is known for multitasking and completing the assigned tasks within the deadline.



#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

#### 2020-2021

#### **WPE Social Worker – IRC / Anbar – Ramadi**

#### During my time here I've been:

- Provide age-appropriate case management to survivors of GBV in line with WPE Case Management guidelines; including assessment of client needs, basic crisis counseling; supporting clients in developing a plan to address their individual needs and safely implementing this plan; support to clients in accessing services from other providers as per their wishes.
- Support in facilitating WGCC activities and psychosocial support group sessions to vulnerable women and girls, and participate in community mapping/safety audit sessions to identify any general protection/GBV concerns from women and girls
- Document and store all case management information and survivor data confidentially and securely, ensure any sharing of survivor information is done with the survivor's informed consent and in-line with best practice as part of the referral procedure

## 2019 – 2020 Administrative AL-AZRA organization / Erbil

#### During my time here I've been:

- Organizing administrative and logistical aspects of office activities and events, including workshops, meetings and book the meeting rooms accordingly.
- Creating, updating, and maintaining records and databases.

# 2018-2019 Accountant – DARYA Company / Sulaymaniyah

## During my time here I've been:

- preparing accounts and tax returns
- administering payrolls and controlling income and expenditure
- auditing financial information
- compiling and presenting reports, budgets, business plans, commentaries and financial statements

## **P**

## **PROFESSIONAL SKILLS**

Critical thinking – Managerial skills – Relationship management – Problem-solving - Computer skills (MS office word –excel – power point - outlook) – Leadership skills – Organization – Interpersonal communication – Collaboration – Time management – Empathy Satirical and analytical skills –internet - email